What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Silin?
يمسح؟
It's okay if you're not used to it.
لا بأس إذا لم تكن معتادًا على ذلك.
We can take it slow.
يمكننا أن نأخذ الأمر ببطء.
Am I that uninteresting to you?
هل أنا غير مثير للاهتمام بالنسبة لك؟
Miss Xu, I'm sorry.
آنسة شو، أنا آسف.
I don't want to lie to you
لا أريد أن أكذب عليك
or to myself.
أو لنفسي.
Miss, something terrible has happened!
آنسة، لقد حدث شيء فظيع!
The Commander is in trouble.
القائد في ورطة.
Yiyu.
ممكن.
Thank goodness you're okay.
الحمد لله أنك بخير.
Thank goodness.
شكرا لله.
No need to explain anything.
لا حاجة لشرح أي شيء.
I saw everything.
لقد رأيت كل شئ.
What did you see?
ماذا رأيت؟
Yiyu.
ممكن.
Let me explain.
دعني أشرح لك.
The truth isn't what you think.
الحقيقة ليست كما تعتقد.
What else is there to say?
ماذا بقي لي أن أقول؟
I never thought you were this kind of person.
لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أنك هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
You're just like Liu Sinan.
أنت تمامًا مثل ليو سينان.
For the Liu family,
بالنسبة لعائلة ليو،
for your own benefit,
لمصلحتك الخاصة،
you'd use anyone
سوف تستخدم أي شخص
and do anything.
وفعل أي شيء.
I didn't.
لم أكن.
It's not what you think.
إنه ليس كما تعتقد.
In your eyes,
في عينيك،
what am I?
ما أنا؟
What do I mean to you?
ماذا أعني لك؟
Just a doll you can play with whenever you want?
مجرد دمية يمكنك اللعب بها وقتما تشاء؟
No,
لا،
not even a doll.
ولا حتى دمية.
Just trash to be thrown away after you're done with it.
مجرد قمامة يتم التخلص منها بعد الانتهاء منها.
Yiyu, I'm absolutely not that kind of person.
يييو، أنا لست من هذا النوع من الأشخاص على الإطلاق.
You have to believe me.
يجب عليك أن تصدقني.
Didn't you say
ألم تقل؟
you would always believe in me no matter what?
هل ستؤمن بي دائمًا مهما حدث؟
But now I regret it.
ولكنني الآن أشعر بالندم.
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
Liu Silin,
ليو سيلين,
I don't want to see you again.
لا أريد رؤيتك مرة أخرى.
I won't hate you either.
أنا لن أكرهك أيضاً
I don't have the strength to hate anyone now.
ليس لدي القوة لأكره أحدا الآن.
Hate...
يكره...
I only hate myself for being so blind.
أنا فقط أكره نفسي لكوني أعمى.
I'm the one who misjudged you.
أنا من أخطأت في الحكم عليك.
I was too foolish.
لقد كنت غبيًا جدًا.
Yiyu.
ممكن.
Father! What's wrong, Father?
أبي! ما بك يا أبي؟
Father! What's happened to you?
أبي! ماذا حدث لك؟
Don't scare me, Father.
لا تخيفني يا أبي.
Daughter.
بنت.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I won't be able to stay with you anymore.
لن أتمكن من البقاء معك بعد الآن.
You must take good care of yourself.
يجب عليك الاعتناء بنفسك جيدًا.
When it's cold,
عندما يكون الجو باردا،
put on more clothes.
إرتدي المزيد من الملابس.
When you're hungry,
عندما تشعر بالجوع،
make sure you eat properly.
تأكد من أنك تأكل بشكل صحيح.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
I've been in Yuncheng.
لقد كنت في يونتشنغ.
I've made many enemies.
لقد صنعت العديد من الأعداء.
Now,
الآن،
they've all come after me.
لقد جاءوا جميعا بعدي.
You're my only family in this world.
أنت عائلتي الوحيدة في هذا العالم.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Don't leave me, Father.
لا تتركني يا أبي.
Go quickly.
اذهب بسرعة.
Go!
يذهب!
Father!
أب!
Go now!
اذهب الآن!
Hurry!
عجل!
Run!
يجري!
Help!
يساعد!
Is anybody there?
هل يوجد أحد هناك؟
Help! Help!
مساعدة! مساعدة!
Help! Murder! Help!
مساعدة! جريمة قتل! مساعدة!
Stop! Help!
توقف!النجدة!
It's you.
إنه أنت.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Come out now.
اخرج الآن.
I can see you.
أستطيع أن أراك.
Don't make a sound.
لا تصدر صوتا.
This way.
من هنا.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
I must thank you for today.
يجب أن أشكرك على اليوم.
No need to thank me, Miss Xu.
لا داعي لشكرني، آنسة شو.
I saved you by mere coincidence.
لقد انقذتك بالصدفة فقط.
Who's trying to kill you?
من يحاول قتلك؟
Shouldn't you
ألا ينبغي لك؟
be with Liu Silin right now?
هل تريد أن تكون مع ليو سيلين الآن؟
You know about my family's recent situation.
أنت تعرف عن الوضع الأخير لعائلتي.
To be honest,
صراحة،
my father has made countless enemies in Yuncheng over the years.
لقد صنع والدي عددًا لا يحصى من الأعداء في يونتشنغ على مر السنين.
Now that he's lost his power,
الآن بعد أن فقد قوته،
these people won't let him go.
هؤلاء الناس لن يسمحوا له بالذهاب.
Just now,
الآن،
he was killed by his enemies.
لقد قتله أعداؤه.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm the one who should apologize to you.
أنا من يجب أن يعتذر لك.
That day at the banquet,
في ذلك اليوم في المأدبة،
I deliberately said I had a past with Silin.
قلت عمدا أن لدي ماضي مع سيلين.
It was just to upset you
لقد كان فقط لإزعاجك
and make you back off.
ويجعلك تتراجع.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Good that you understand.
من الجيد أنك فهمت.
No matter what I did,
بغض النظر عما فعلته،
Silin's heart and thoughts
قلب سيلين وأفكاره
are always with you.
أنا معك دائمًا.
Don't misunderstand him.
لا تسيء فهمه.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
you don't need to speak up for him.
لا تحتاج إلى التحدث نيابة عنه.
Aren't you curious
ألا تشعر بالفضول؟
why the police station suddenly released you?
لماذا أطلق مركز الشرطة سراحك فجأة؟
Hmm.
همم.
Liu Silin made a deal with me
لقد عقد ليو سيلين صفقة معي
to save you.
لإنقاذك.
I arranged for Chief Wang to release you
لقد رتبت مع رئيس وانغ لإطلاق سراحك
on the condition that he would be with me.
بشرط أن يكون معي.
But
لكن
he wouldn't even touch me.
حتى أنه لم يلمسني.
You're the only one in his heart.
أنت الوحيد في قلبه.
You mean
هل تقصد
he did it to save me?
هل فعل ذلك لإنقاذي؟
You took the blame for him.
لقد تحملت اللوم عنه.
And now he saved you like this.
والآن أنقذك هكذا.
You two share such a deep bond.
أنتم الاثنان تتقاسمان رابطة عميقة جدًا.
I'm truly envious.
أنا أشعر بالحسد حقا.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Go find him now!
اذهب للبحث عنه الآن!
Thank you, Miss Xu.
شكرا لك، آنسة شو.
Silin.
يمسح.
I understand now.
انا أفهم الآن.
I misunderstood you completely.
لقد أساءت فهمك تماما.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
It's all in the past.
كل هذا في الماضي.
Everything's fine now.
كل شئ على ما يرام الآن.
Are you really planning to leave Yuncheng?
هل تخطط حقًا لمغادرة يونتشنغ؟
My father is gone.
لقد رحل والدي.
There's nothing left in Yuncheng worth staying for.
لم يعد هناك شيء في يونتشنغ يستحق البقاء من أجله.
If you need anything,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء،
just ask.
فقط اسأل.
We'll help if we can.
سنساعدك إذا استطعنا.
Thank you, Yiyu.
شكرا لك، يييو.
I wish you both happiness.
أتمنى لكم السعادة.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
I remember once...
أتذكر مرةً...
Liu Sinan and my father were talking at the commander's mansion.
وكان ليو سينان ووالدي يتحدثان في قصر القائد.
They mentioned something about
لقد ذكروا شيئا عن
my father helping him find
والدي يساعده في العثور على
a German revolver.
مسدس ألماني.
I don't know if this information
لا أعلم إذا كانت هذه المعلومات
is useful to you.
هل هو مفيد لك؟
I understand. Thank you.
انا أفهم. شكرا لك.
Silin.
يمسح.
You should go back first.
ينبغي عليك العودة أولاً.
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Young master, you're back.
سيدي الشاب، لقد عدت.
We've all been waiting for your return.
لقد كنا جميعا ننتظر عودتك.
The young master is back.
لقد عاد السيد الشاب.
Young master.
سيد شاب.
I'm so glad you're alright.
أنا سعيد جدًا لأنك بخير.
During your absence these past few days,
خلال غيابك في الأيام القليلة الماضية،
we were completely at a loss and worried sick,
لقد كنا في حيرة تامة وقلق شديد،
afraid that Fulu Restaurant might close down again.
خائف من أن مطعم فولو قد يغلق مرة أخرى.
Do you even know how to speak properly?
هل تعرف حتى كيفية التحدث بشكل صحيح؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Yiyu and I will never abandon everyone.
أنا ويييو لن نتخلى عن الجميع أبدًا.
What are you standing around for?
لماذا تقف هنا؟
Get back to work.
العودة إلى العمل.
Yes, young master.
نعم سيدي الشاب.
If Commander Xu
إذا كان القائد شو
really helped Liu Sinan forge a revolver,
لقد ساعد ليو سينان حقًا في صنع مسدس،
then it's very likely
إذن فمن المرجح جدًا
that the real killer of Xiuhe
أن القاتل الحقيقي لشيوهي
is Liu Sinan.
هو ليو سينان.
We need to investigate this matter further.
نحن بحاجة إلى التحقيق في هذه المسألة بشكل أكبر.
Yu
يو
[Credits]
[الاعتمادات]